question_data = [
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "In the Resident Evil series, Leon S. Kennedy is a member of STARS.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "In career mode of Need for Speed: Underground 2, the first car the player can drive is the BMW M3 GTR.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "Nintendo started out as a playing card manufacturer.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "Amazon acquired Twitch in August 2014 for $970 million dollars.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "In Call Of Duty: Zombies, you can upgrade the Apothicon Servant in the Shadows Of Evil map.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "The Sniper's SMG in Team Fortress 2, was originally intended to be the Scout&#039;s primary weapon.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "In Monster Hunter Generations, guild style is a type of hunting style.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "During pre-production of Super Mario Bros., Mario originally was meant to shoot bullets.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "The Ace Attorney trilogy was suppose to end with Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney; Trials and Tribulations as its final game.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "TF2: The Heavy's voice actor, Gary Schwartz, voices the Demoman as well ",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    }
]
